<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourGuide</string>
    <string name="charminar">Charminar</string>
    <string name="charminar_location">Ghansi Bazaar,Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="tourist_places">Tourist Places</string>
    <string name="restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="temples">Temples</string>
    <string name="malls">Malls</string>
    <string name="falaknuma_palace">Falaknuma Palace</string>
    <string name="falaknuma_location">Falaknuma,Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="ramoji_film_city">Ramoji Film City</string>
    <string name="ramoji_film_city_location">Hayathnagar,Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="golconda">Golconda</string>
    <string name="golconda_location">Ibrahimbagh,Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="hussain_sagar">Hussain Sagar</string>
    <string name="hussain_sagar_location">Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="absolutebarbeque">Absolute Barbeque</string>
    <string name="absolute_barbeque_location">Gachibowli,Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="flechazo">Flechazo</string>
    <string name="flechazo_location">Madhapur,Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="prego">Prego</string>
    <string name="prego_location">Hitec City,Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="paradise">Paradise</string>
    <string name="paradise_location">Gachibowli,Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="water_front">Water Front</string>
    <string name="water_front_location">Necklace Road,Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="birlamandir">Birla Mandir</string>
    <string name="birlamandir_location">Khairatabad,Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="chilkur_temple">Chilkur Balaji Temple</string>
    <string name="chilkur_temple_location">Chilukuru,Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="hanuman_temple">Karmanghat Hanuman Temple</string>
    <string name="hanuman_temple_location">Karmanghat,Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="jagannath_temple">Jagannath Temple</string>
    <string name="jagannath_temple_location">Banjara Hills,Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="keesara_temple">Keesaragutta</string>
    <string name="keesara_temple_location">Keesara,Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="forum_mall">Forum Mall</string>
    <string name="forum_mall_location">JNTU,Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="inorbit_mall">Inorbit Mall</string>
    <string name="inorbit_mall_location">Madhapur,Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="next_galleria_mall">Next Galleria Mall</string>
    <string name="next_galleria_mall_location">Punjagutta,Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="cinepolis_mall">Cinepolis Mall</string>
    <string name="cinepolis_mall_location">KPHB,Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="manjeera_mall">Manjeera Mall</string>
    <string name="manjeera_mall_location">Kukatpally,Hyderabad</string>
    <string name="forum_mall_desc">Forum Sujana Mall is a shopping mall located at Kukatpally. Zara made their Hyderabad debut at The Forum Sujana Mall. The mall houses a 9-screen multiplex from PVR Cinemas</string>
    <string name="inorbit_mall_desc">Inorbit Mall is a subsidiary of the Evo enterprises and K. Raheja Corporation which runs shopping malls in various parts of India.The first Inorbit Mall opened in 2004, in Malad, Mumbai.Inorbit Malls launched their second property in Navi Mumbai at Vashi, in October 2008,third in Hyderabad in October 2009.</string>
    <string name="manjeera_mall_desc">Manjeera mall is a mall located in kukatpally within a very small place with limited options for shopping and eating but economical.</string>
    <string name="next_galleria_mall_desc">Next Galleria Mall is a very popular mall located in punjagutta established by PVR group.It has good options for shopping,eating and for watching movies.</string>
    <string name="cinepolis_mall_desc">Cinépolis is a Mexican chain of movie theaters. Its name means City of Cinema and its slogan is La Capital del Cine.It has branches also in India with nice quality infrastructures and availability.</string>
    <string name="karmanghat_desc">The Karmanghat Hanuman Temple is one of the oldest and popular Hindu temples in Hyderabad, in the state of Telangana, India. The presiding deity of the temple is Lord Hanuman</string>
    <string name="chilkur_desc">Chilkur Balaji Temple, popularly known as "Visa Balaji Temple'', is an ancient Hindu temple of Lord Balaji on the banks of Osman Sagar in Hyderabad. It is one of the oldest temples in Hyderabad built during the time of Madanna and Akkanna, the uncles of Bhakta Ramadas.</string>
    <string name="jagannath_desc">The Jagannath Temple in Hyderabad, India is a modern temple built by the Odia community of the city of Hyderabad dedicated to the Hindu God Jagannath. The temple located near Banjara hills Road no.12 (twelve) in Hyderabad is famous for its annual Rathyatra festival attended by thousands of devotees</string>
    <string name="keesara_desc">Keesaragutta Temple is a Hindu temple dedicated to Lord Siva and his consorts Bhavani and Sivadurga at Keesaragutta in Medchal-Malkajgiri district. It is about 30 km from Hyderabad and 12 km from ECIL. It is located on a small hillock. The temple draws up to lakhs of devotees on Shivaratri and karthika masam</string>
    <string name="birla_mandir_desc">Birla Mandir is a Hindu temple, built on a 280 feet (85 m) high hillock called Naubath Pahad on a 13 acres (53,000 m2) plot. The construction took 10 years and was opened in 1976 by Swami Ranganathananda of Ramakrishna Mission. The temple was constructed by Birla Foundation, which has also constructed several similar temples across India, all of which are known as Birla Mandir</string>
    <string name="absolute_barbeque_desc">Absoulte barbeque is a chain of costly restaurants usually serves buffet(veg and non-veg) with all types of kebabs and fooditems.</string>
    <string name="water_front_desc">Water Front is a famous restaurant in front of the water body Hussain Sagar usually serves all types of food and wine and usually economical.</string>
    <string name="prego_desc">Prego is a modern hub with a poolside patio at the Westin Hotel serving Italian classics, cocktails and wine located in the area of hitec city.</string>
    <string name="flechazo_desc">Flechazo is a five star restaurant in nearby area of madhapur usually economical and good taste foods are served.</string>
    <string name="paradise_desc">The Paradise restaurant, founded in 1953, began as a small cafe serving tea and snacks, but now it serves traditional Hyderabadi, Indian and Chinese continental delicacies. The hotel is known for Hyderabadi dishes.</string>
    <string name="ramoji_film_dity_desc">The Ramoji Film City in India is located in Hyderabad. Spread over 2000 acres,it is the largest integrated film city in Telangana and has been certified by the Guinness World Records as the largest studio complex in the world.It was built by Telugu film producer Ramoji Rao in 1996</string>
    <string name="hussainsagar_desc">Hussain Sagar is a heart shaped lake in Hyderabad built by Ibrahim Quli Qutb Shah, and named after Hussain Shah Wali. It is spread across an area of 5.7 square kilometers and is fed by River Musi. A large monolithic statue of the Gautama Buddha, erected in 1992, stands on Gibraltar Rock in the middle of the lake</string>
    <string name="golconda_desc">Golkonda, also known as Golconda, Gol konda ("Round shaped hill"), or Golla konda, (Shepherd\'s Hill) is a citadel and fort in Southern India and was the capital of the medieval sultanate of the Qutb Shahi dynasty (c.1518–1687), is situated 11 km (6.8 mi) west of Hyderabad. It is also a tehsil of Hyderabad district, Telangana, India</string>
    <string name="falaknuma_desc">Falaknuma is a palace in Hyderabad, Telangana, India. It belonged to the Paigah family, and was later owned by the Nizam of Hyderabad.It is on a 32-acre (13 ha) area in Falaknuma, 5 km from Charminar. It was built by Nawab Sir Vikhar-ul-Umra - Prime Minister of Hyderabad and the uncle and brother-in-law of the sixth Nizam.Falak-numa means "Like the Sky" or "Mirror of the Sky" in Urdu.</string>
    <string name="charminar_desc">The Charminar ("Four Minarets"), constructed in 1591, is a monument and mosque located in Hyderabad, Telangana, India. The landmark has become a global icon of Hyderabad, listed among the most recognized structures of India. Charminar has been a historical place with mosque on the top floor for over 400 years and also famous for its surrounding markets. It is one of the tourist attractions in Hyderabad.</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
